提高退休年齡
Raising the age of retirement
是對美國夢不可容忍的侵蝕
is an unacceptable erosion of the American Dream.
如果共和黨無法通過福利改革
If the Republicans fail to pass a reasonable Omnibus package
達成合理的綜合解決方案
by demanding entitlement reform,
就會迫使聯邦政府凍結開銷
they will force the federal government into a spending freeze.
凍瘡會長在他們手上  不是我們手上
The frostbite will be on their hands. Not ours.
這句是不是有點過了  凍瘡那句
Do you think that's a bit much? The frostbite bit?
這是國情諮文  先生
Well, it's the State of the Union, sir.
我們想爭取中部各州的贊同
We want to appeal to the flyover states.
他們會喜歡那句話的
They'll like that line.
我想要點更有力的句子
I want something more forceful.
他們手上沾滿血
Blood on their hands?
不行
No.
把我們丟回冰河紀
Throw us back into the ice age.
我喜歡那句  克里斯蒂娜  我們試試
I like that, Christina. Let's try that.
琳達  克里斯蒂娜  你也過來
Linda. Christina, you come up here, too.
世上有兩種副總統
There are two types of vice presidents.
受氣包和鬥牛士
Doormats and matadors.
你覺得我想做那種呢
Which do you think I intend to be?
雷蒙德
Raymond.
他在為內政操心
He's hung up on the domestic agenda.
一句關於中國的話也沒說
Not a single word about China.
他的直覺是對的
His instincts are right.
如果政府在演講後第二天關門
If the government shuts down one day after the speech,
他講了什麼就完全不重要了
not a single word in the speech matters.
我們得馬上解決凍結開銷的問題
We have to address the freeze now.
中國的事得靠後
China comes later.
兩黨為了改革的事吵了幾個月了
Both parties have been wrangling over entitlements for months.
未來三天裡
What makes you think a miracle
怎麼可能出現奇蹟
is gonna happen in the next three days?
我們給共和黨他們想要的
We give the Republicans exactly what they want.
退休年齡
Retirement age?
對
Yes.
那是不可跨越的界限
That's a line in the sand we cannot cross.
我們最終還是得跨  所以何必爭下去呢
We will cross it eventually, so why keep fighting it?
我可以推動參議院通過法案
I can push this through the Senate.
一旦我做到  總統就能在國情諮文中
And once I do, the president will announce
宣佈兩黨達成了一項重要協議
a major bipartisan agreement in the State of the Union.
我們避免了政府關門
We avoid a government shutdown,
而功勞歸白宮
and the White House gets credit.
太冒險了
It's a huge risk.
一旦失敗  會顏面掃地
And if it fails, a huge embarrassment.
那也是丟我的臉
The embarrassment will be entirely my own.
這事我來擔
This is on my shoulders.
即使如此  也不好說服總統
Even so, the president is gonna require some serious persuasion.
我去跟他談
I'm happy to talk to him.
別  我來吧
No. No. I'll do it.
朋友去說  他更容易接受
He'll be more amenable if it comes from a friend.
沒錯  可信的密友
You're right. A trusted confidant.
我去試試水吧
Let me test the waters.
塔斯克黨  成員  一人
The Cult of Tusk. Membership: one.
不過那個信徒恰好是
But that one disciple just so happens to be
自由世界最有權力的人
the most powerful man in the free world.
至少目前還是
For now.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
翻譯 某羽   某豚   somehacker   章魚X   葉某人
翻譯 艾瑞卡   肉鬆   盧克·天意   小飯
藍光版調整  timhal@HDWinG字幕組   後期 餓得慌
顧問 老杜   校對 草草   總監 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻譯 HDWinG字幕組修正 請勿去掉製作者資訊
《紙牌屋》
第二季  第三集
福利改革  把退休年齡提到67歲
The entitlements. Raising the age of eligibility to 67.
你們那邊不會同意的
Your people will never go for it.
領導層同意  他們就會點頭
They will if the leadership does.
而領導層會同意的
And the leadership will.
我還沒斷奶時這事就是兩黨的爭議焦點
They fought us on this since I was in diapers.
假如我能說服我黨同意提高退休年齡
Assuming that I can get this past my people and convince them,
你能說服你那邊嗎
can you convince yours?
這很困難
It's a tough sell.
你是參議院多數黨領袖  赫克特
You're the Senate majority leader, Hector.
你不需要遊說  可以直接命令
You don't have to sell. You can dictate.
你想要什麼回報
What do you want in return?
一個正常運轉的政府  避免開銷凍結
A working government. We stave off the freeze.
你在《教育法案》上贏了
You won on education.
我們讓你當上了副總統
We confirmed you as vice president.
共和黨需要贏一次  弗蘭克
The Republicans need a win, Frank.
我就是在提供贏的機會
And that's what I'm offering.
你們在福利改革上贏了
You get a win on entitlements.
我們避免了關門
We avoid a shutdown.
兩黨合作  雙方都得分
Everyone gets points for bipartisanship.
你知道我擔心誰
You know who I'm worried about.
柯蒂斯·哈斯
Curtis Haas.
他是個麻煩  弗蘭克
He's a troublemaker, Frank.
還控制了你三分之一的黨內成員
Who controls a third of your caucus.
他絕不會同意的
And he'll never go for this.
他就想看民主黨不好過
He wants to see the Democrats suffer.
讓他考慮一下
Just bring him to the table.
我只求這個
That's all I'm asking.
蓋拉格小姐  我叫盧卡斯·古德溫
Miss Gallagher? My name is Lucas Goodwin.
我是《華盛頓先驅報》的副主編
I'm a deputy editor at the Washington Herald.
古德溫先生  拜託了
Mr. Goodwin, please.
只需要幾分鐘  我不求別的
Just a few moments. That's all I'm asking.
如果我想跟你說話  就會回你的電話
If I wanted to talk to you, I would have returned your calls.
你讀過我的郵件嗎
Did you read my emails?
讀了  所以我沒聯繫你
Yes. Which is why I didn't call.
請給我個機會解釋
Give me a chance to walk you through it.
我得趕回白宮
I have to get back to the White House.
-抱歉  -彼得·羅素是被殺害的
- I'm sorry. - Peter Russo was killed.
放手
Let go.
佐伊·巴恩斯也是  我跟她是同事
So was Zoe Barnes. I was working with her.
住口  聽我說...
Stop and listen --
弗蘭克·安德伍德是幕後黑手
Frank Underwood is the one who did this.
聽著  這是一派胡言
Listen! This is nuts.
酒駕記錄  聽證會  所有都是...
The DUI. The brack hearing. All of it was part of --
你不能再這樣了  好嗎
This has to stop. Okay?
安德伍德找過你了嗎
Did Underwood talk to you?
-讓你不要和別人說這些事嗎  -沒有
- Tell you not to speak with anybody? - No.
道格·斯坦普嗎
Doug Stamper?
無論你以為發生了什麼
Whatever you think happened,
無論是什麼讓你這樣跟蹤我...
whatever compelled you to stalk me like this --
你是唯一可能知道點什麼的人
You're the only person who might know something,
能理解得了的人
who could understand.
我沒有別人可以說這事了
I've got -- I've got no one else I can talk --
我不理解  也不想理解
I don't understand. And I don't want to.
行嗎  這裡面沒什麼內情
Okay? There's no story here.
拜託了  只要五分鐘
Please, just five minutes.
想想你自己的行為
Just think about what you're doing.
守在樓外
Waiting outside of a building --
如果不是弗蘭克·安德伍德  彼得可能還活著
Peter would still be alive if it wasn't for Frank Underwood.
我花了很大力氣忘記彼得的事
I've worked really hard to put Peter behind me.
如果我再看到你  你再來找我
So if I see you again, if I hear from you again,
我不僅會報警
I'll not only contact the police,
還會讓副總統知道你在對他說三道四
I'll let the vice president know what you're saying about him,
到時候你就等著特勤局來找上門吧
and then you can deal with the Secret Service, too.
都是正常的海外聲音  中國那邊有些雜音
It's the usual overseas chatter. Bit of a bum in China,
但我們覺得原因在貿易緊張
but we chalk that up to the trade tensions.
特勤局
Secret Service.
總統和副總統收到的死亡威脅數正常
Average number of death threats to both POTUS and the VP.
我們都交給了聯調局的好夥伴們
We passed them along to our dear friends at the FBI.
聯調局呢
FBI?
聯調局向我們特勤局的
The FBI confirms the level of activity
好夥伴們確認了活動程度
of our dear friends at the Secret Service.
我們全部進行了追蹤調查  沒有高階別的威脅
We followed up on everything. No high-level threats.
我們沒有需要直接
So nothing we need to report directly
向總統和副總統彙報的內容嗎
to the president or vice president?
-沒有  -謝謝  先生們
- No. - Thank you, gentlemen.
你發的郵件還有別人看過嗎
The email you sent. Has anyone else seen it?
除了告知我的特工外  沒有了
Except for the agent that alerted me, no.
其他機構可能會偶然看到
Other agencies might have stumbled upon this.
即使如此  他們大概也不會在意
Even so, they probably ignored it.
知道是誰發的帖子嗎
Any idea who's making the posts?
深網論壇
Deep Web forums.
幾乎無法追蹤  很可能就是一個人
Almost impossible to trace. Lone wolf most likely.
我要你找到這個人
I want you to find him.
得有對生命構成直接威脅的證據
We need a direct threat to life.
副總統剛剛上任
The vice president just assumed office.
這類陰謀論絕不能甚囂塵上
I can't have this conspiracy stuff going mainstream.
-這類傳言一般會漸漸平息  -我不能冒這個險
- This sort of thing usually fizzles out -- - I can't take the chance.
你去找到這個人  把他關起來
I want you to find him and put him away.
-他並沒犯罪  -但他有這個傾向
- He hasn't committed a crime. - But he wants to.
那就來個推波助瀾
So help him.
那要耗費人力
That requires manpower.
你手裡有人
You've got men.
會暴露我的  道格
It exposes me, Doug.
我一直給你透露訊息  因為你是老朋友了
I've always kept you informed because you're an old pal
我信任你  但...
and I trust you. But...
你這是要我展開正式行動
We're talking about an operation.
我是你在白宮工作的老朋友
I'm an old pal who now works at the White House.
老朋友之間說說
Between old pals,
我這個行政部門聯絡官已經當得太久了
I've been stuck as the executive liaison for way too long.
您是否擔心
How worried are you
您所在社羣的學校內會發生大規模槍擊事件
that a mass shooting could happen in a school in your community?
非常擔心  比較擔心  不怎麼擔心
Great deal, somewhat, not so much,
完全不擔心  還是不確定
not at all, unsure?
你的聲音很性感嘛  人怎麼樣
You sound hot. Are you hot?
先生
Sir...
比較性感  非常性感
Somewhat hot? A great deal hot?
掛斷
林奇堡兒童醫院  電話  傳真
這裡是林奇堡兒童醫院小兒科
Lynchburg Children's, Pediatric Division.
我找謝莉爾·波斯納
Can I talk to Cheryl Posner?
抱歉  她正在值班
Sorry. She's on duty right now.
我是她女兒
It's her daughter.
請稍候
Hold on one moment.
瑞秋  瑞秋嗎
Rachel? Rachel?
甜心  你在聽嗎  請別...
Sweetheart, are you there? Please, do--
掛斷
您好
Hello?
您好  傑伊先生
Hello, Mr. Jay.
我叫瑞秋
My name is Rachel
代表全國槍支教育中心向您致電
and I'm calling on behalf of the National Firearm Education Center.
您能和我簡單聊聊
Would you be able to speak with me briefly
您對槍支立法和第二修正案的看法嗎
regarding firearm legislation and Second Amendment legislation?
你就是薇拉力薦的人
So, you're Willa's top choice.
那我丈夫和我為什麼要選擇你呢
Why should you be my husband's and my top choice?
在過去十年中
Over the past 10 years
關於你們夫婦的報道加起來還不到
the two of you combined have gotten less coverage
內布拉斯加州資淺眾議員的平均水平
than the average junior congressman from Nebraska.
我們不想太受矚目
Well, we don't seek the spotlight.
我不是說你們非要如此
I'm not suggesting you should.
但如果我沒猜錯
But am I correct in assuming
你丈夫會是一位行事積極的副總統
that your husband will be an active vice president?
想讓媒體不去關注積極的副總統是比較難的
It's harder to keep an active VP out of the press than in it,
但我們可以讓媒體剛好有些料可追
but it's possible if we give the media just enough
不至於什麼都拿不到
to keep them from starving.
你在哪長大的  康納
Where'd you grow up, Connor?
德州  和你一樣
Texas. Just like you.
達拉斯嗎
Dallas?
拉布克
Lubbock.
我想改口音可比你們難多了
I had a much thicker accent to get rid of you than y'all.
你怎麼知道我有口音
How do you know I had one?
你倆第一次共同接受採訪
Your first joint interview,
86年你丈夫競選州議員時
when your husband was running for state assembly in '86.
網上有嗎
That's on the internet?
沒有  我聯繫了格林維爾當地的電視臺
No. No. I contacted the local affiliate in Greenville.
他們不願郵寄錄影帶
They wouldn't send me the tapes via mail,
我就親自去資料庫看了
so I went down there and watched in their vault.
跑到南卡羅萊納嗎
To South Carolina?
應聘就得做好準備工作
When I want a job, I do my homework.
很期待你的表現
I look forward to seeing what you come up with.
謝謝  安德伍德太太
Thank you, Mrs. Underwood.
週四見
Thursday.
這怎麼能算勝利
I don't see how this is a victory for us.
我們要麼面臨開銷凍結
Our choices are the freeze,
民主黨會為這個飽受責難
which the Democrats get blamed for, or --
不一定  共和...
Not necessarily. The Republi--
我們也一樣會受責難
No, which we definitely get blamed for.
-要麼給他們  -福利改革嗎  弗蘭克
- Or we offer them -- - Entitlements, Frank?
我們已經表了態  不能回頭了
We took a stand. We can't turn back now.
我寧可讓政府停轉
I'd rather see the government grind to a halt.
如果頭條是
Think of the headline:
《民主黨高層通過法案  避免開銷凍結》
"Democrat Leadership Enacts Entitlement Reform, Staves Off Freeze."
這是團結和進步的表現
We show unity. We offer progress.
我們說服幾個中堅保守派吧
Let's convert some lifelong conservatives.
門多薩答應合作了嗎
You have Mendoza's assurance he'll work with us?
是的
I do.
我可不想把頭伸出去
I don't want to put our necks out there
等人家落刀
just to have the guillotine fall.
不會的  我們也會一起伸出去
You won't. My neck will be right out there with you.
弗蘭西斯暈血
Francis faints at the sight of blood.
不會允許他們割傷他的面板的
He'd never let them break the skin.
敬團結
To unity.
不不不  別這樣
No, no, no, no, no. Come on.
拉瑞  能來一趟嗎
Larry, can you come by?
我電腦不知道怎麼了
Something weird's going on with my computer.
謝謝
Thanks.
別這樣
Come on!
怎麼回事
Hey, what's the problem?
沒事  我修好了
Nothing. It's fine. Uh, I fixed it.
好吧
Okay. Cool.
放鬆
深呼吸
投降吧
你要的我能給你  親愛的
還不夠革新
It's not as progressive as I'd like.
不夠極端吧
You mean radical.
退休年齡升到67歲  2055年前政府都能負擔福利
Raising retirement age to 67 makes entitlements solvent until 2055.
還能省一萬億
And it saves us over a trillion dollars
不花納稅人的錢
without a single penny of taxpayer income.
改到68歲能再省三千億
68 would give us another 300 billion.
我還想禁止提前退休
And I'd like to eliminate early retirement.
完全禁止嗎
Entirely?
不可能
Forget it.
68歲退  64歲早退呢
What about 68 and 64?
我要對選民負責
I have a responsibility to my constituents.
我承諾過某些問題絕不妥協
I promised I wouldn't waver when it comes to things --
民共兩黨票數僵持時  茶黨的傾向能決定局勢
難道要讓茶黨決定財政立法嗎
Are we really going to allow the Tea Party to determine fiscal legislation?
我從沒指望他們幫忙
I've never been beholden to the Tea Party.
得了吧  柯蒂斯
Come on, Curtis.
沒有茶黨政治行動委員會
You wouldn't have won reelection
給你的一千萬  你也贏不了重選
if their PACs hadn't dumped 10 million into your campaign.
如果他們對縮減開支的看法
If their definition of budgetary conservatism
與我不謀而合  那就正好...
happens to overlap with mine, that's a function--
柯蒂斯  柯蒂斯  友善一點
Curtis. Curtis. Let's show some goodwill.
68歲和64歲可以接受嗎
Can you stomach 68 and 64?
馬上生效嗎
Effective immediately?
五年以後
Five years from now.
沒興趣
Not interested.
我們不能突然拋出這個提議
Well, you know we can't throw this on people without any warning.
得給他們時間消化
They need some time to digest.
對不起  就是不行
I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
好吧  回去跟你們的幕僚和同事商量一下
Okay. Meet with your staff. Consult with your colleagues.
我也回去商量  明天再談
I'll consult with mine. And let's talk tomorrow.
好吧  沒問題
All right. I can agree to that.
這第一步很不錯
But this is a good first step.
修正案通過後  法案進行表決時
How do we make sure Curtis can't filibuster
柯蒂斯阻撓議事怎麼辦
when we get the amendment passed?
如果能走到那步
Assuming we do.
只跟你說  我覺得我們可以改變他的想法
Between you and me, I'm sure we can turn him around.
我只是不想冒險
I just want to be on the safe side.
我們讓修正案的表決
We make sure the passage of the amendment
成為法案表決的一部分
constitutes the passage of the bill.
事先約定
By previous agreement.
沒錯  修正案一通過
Yeah, that's right. We pass the amendment,
就完事了
and then we're done. Wham, bam.
能落到紙上嗎
Can we put that in writing?
讓艾瑞克森找我吧
Have Erikson reach out to me.
非常感謝
Muchos gracias.
慢用
There you go.
盧卡斯·古德溫
Lucas Goodwin?
開啟我  親愛的
晚上好  盧卡斯
Good evening, Lucas.
對著麥克風說話
Speak into the microphone.
你是誰
Who are you?
返回主屏  開啟另一個應用
Go to the home screen. Open the other app.
先告訴我你是誰
Tell me who you are.
你調查過我  想必已經知道我是誰了
You've done your research. You know who I am.
我怎麼知道那是不是你的真實身份
I -- I know who you claim to be.
你要是現在還不相信我  那就不必談了
And if you're not convinced by now, goodbye.
別別
Wait.
聽你的  我返回主屏了
All right, I'm on the home screen.
開啟驗證程式
Open the notary app.
這是什麼
What is this?
確保你不為執法部門工作
To ensure you aren't law enforcement.
我不是
I'm -- I'm not.
那就簽了它
Then sign.
怎麼簽
How?
把你的拇指按在攝像頭上  然後點"掃描"
Hold your thumb to the camera and press "Capture."
身份驗證  指紋掃描
萬一你是給執法部門的呢
How do I know you're not law enforcement?
要麼簽了這檔案  要麼走人
Sign the document or walk away.
身份驗證  指紋掃描
好了  我簽好了
All right. I did it.
點"發送"
Press "Send."
發送到哪
Where is this going?
我用了伊朗和其他12個國家的代理
I'm VPNing through Iran and 12 other countries.
你不用擔心  連結很安全
Don't worry. It's secure.
最後一件事
Now, one last thing.
我要《華盛頓先驅報》
I need the two-step verification code
內部伺服器的兩步驗證碼
for the Herald's internal servers.
我根本不知道該怎麼做
I -- I don't -- I don't even know how to do that.
你當然知道  看你的郵箱
Yes, you do. Check your email.
把這平板毀了  尤其要把產品序列號抹乾淨
Destroy the iPad, especially the serial number
郵件記牢之後就刪掉
and delete the email after you've memorized it.
祝你好運
Good luck.
還在嗎
Hello?
雷蒙德  還在聽嗎
Raymond, are you there?
在
Yeah.
抱歉  弗蘭克  我還以為看到了一只印加地鳩
Sorry, Frank. I -- I thought I saw an Inca dove.
肯定是冬遷飛錯方向了
Must have flown the wrong direction for winter.
你那邊好像風挺大  你在哪呢
It sounds windy. Where are you?
在我家樓頂  裝了個野鳥餵食器
Top of my building. Got a bird feeder up here.
總統的工作做得不錯  聽說他同意了
Nice work with the President. I hear we have a green light.
他一開始也不願意  但還是讓步了
He pushed back in the beginning, but yeah.
他的寫手正在改講稿
His writers are reworking the speech now.
我這邊也快成了  五年後  68退休  64早退
I'm very close to a deal.  68/64 in five years.
按說好的削減開支
Spending cuts as discussed.
說定了嗎
Is that rock solid?
就差握手簽字了
Soon as we shake hands.
那是誰在作梗
What's the hold-up?
柯蒂斯·哈斯  不過也在意料之中
Curtis Haas, which isn't a surprise.
我過會兒就和他見面  他是最後的障礙了
I'm meeting with him soon. He's the final hurdle.
時間掐得太正好了  弗蘭克
Cutting it pretty close, Frank.
這可是歷史性的時刻
Well, this is -- this is historic.
約翰遜當總統時共和黨人就想推動福利改革了
The Republicans have wanted entitlement reform since Johnson.
柯蒂斯會同意的
Curtis will come around.
另外我們得在講稿裡提到延遲退休的事
In the meantime we should get the new retirement age into the speech.
我看還是別說得太詳細  弗蘭克
I would stay away from the specifics, Frank.
就算參議院通過了  眾議院沒準也...
I mean, I-- even if it passes, the House might--
我對眾議院的瞭解
I know the House better
比你對鳥深入得多  雷蒙德
than you know birds, Raymond.
相信我  他們肯定會通過參議院的版本
Believe me when I say they'll pass the Senate version.
那我去跟總統說說
I'll talk to the President.
但這事絕不能有差錯
Just make sure this is airtight.
多謝你  什麼事
Thank you. What is it?
盧卡斯·古德溫
Lucas Goodwin.
先驅報的那個
From the Herald.
他肯定在和佐伊一起調查
He must have been working with Zoe.
他知道多少
How much does he know?
不會比她多
No more than she did.
她知道的可不少
She knew enough.
我在辦  先生
I'm on it, sir.
有證據嗎
Proof?
還沒有
Not yet.
怎麼搞的  道格
Jesus, Doug.
局面在控制中  我只是想告訴你一聲
It's under control. I just thought you should be aware.
我在跟總統  共和黨和塔斯克周旋
I'm juggling the President, the Republicans, Tusk.
-我不能...  -你就繼續忙你的
- I can't -- - And you should stay focused on that.
古德溫交給我處理  你無須擔心
Goodwin's on my plate. Not yours.
一直到20世紀
It wasn't until the 20th century
客觀主義理念才成為主流觀念
that the notion of noble objectivism came into the forefront.
但事實就是事實
But facts are facts.
1992年  事實  有人拿出一張
1992. Fact: George Bush, Sr.
老布什詢問售貨掃描機是如何工作的照片
is shown asking how a grocery scanner works,
進而攻擊他無知
and he gets nailed for it.
真相是  他們向他展示的是一個新模型機
Fact? They were showing him a new model.
他只是在問新機器與舊機器的差別
He was asking how the new one was different than the old one.
好奇而已  並非無知
Curiosity, not ignorance.
但語境的缺失卻傳達了一個更有衝擊力的觀點
But the lack of context told a more powerful narrative.
在對事實的諸多整理中
There is no arrangement of acts
沒有哪個是...完全客觀的
that is, uh, purely objective.
我們總算可以做點什麼了  終於有手段了
We can finally do something. We have the means to act.
哪個毛都沒長全的少年黑客...
Some teenage pimple-faced hacker --
這是很高階的入侵
This was a sophisticated infiltration.
不是小孩子做得出來的
It's not the work of a child.
你看  郵件在這裡
Look. Here's the email.
機器人希洛尼摩斯
Hieronymus Bot.
希洛尼摩斯  古希臘史學家  以公正著名
聯邦調查局已經追捕他很多年了
The FBI's been hunting him for years.
盧卡斯  聽我說
Lucas, listen to me --
如果我們拿到了這些記錄
If we get these records,
我需要你幫忙理順時間先後
I'll need your help tracking timelines,
拼湊整件事的發展...
piecing together the chronology of the --
不  你只想找個人安慰你
No. You want somebody to hold your hand
告訴你  做這些無用功沒什麼不對
and say it's okay to go on this fucking goose chase.
你不該在伊薩卡教書  你的能力不止如此
You shouldn't be teaching in Ithaca. You're better than that.
-你該回華盛頓  -我就該待在這裡
- You should be back home -- - I belong here.
對一群宿醉未消的英語專業大學生嘮叨嗎
Droning on to a bunch of hungover English majors?
沒錯
Exactly.
你對真相的看法是錯的  客觀事實是存在的
You're wrong about the truth. There is objective truth.
他殺了她
He killed her.
你知道這是事實
You know it's a fact.
事實就是
Here's a fact.
我媽最多只剩10到15年了
My mom has 10, 15 years left at best.
我畢業後加起來也沒有上個月跟她相處時間久
I've seen her more in the past month than since I left for school.
這裡更簡單  也很安靜
It's simpler here. It's quiet.
我需要這樣的環境  她需要我
I need that. She needs me.
很抱歉  盧卡斯
I'm sorry, Lucas.
抱歉我那晚做出了那樣的反應
I'm sorry that night how I reacted.
很遺憾你失去了你的女友
I'm sorry you lost your girlfriend.
很遺憾世界就是這麼操蛋
I'm sorry the world is this fucked up.
我是真心的
I really am.
但我幫不了你
But I can't help you.
其他人在哪裡
Where's everyone else?
我昨天給你幫了個倒忙
I did you a disservice yesterday.
不該在整個領導層面前讓你為難
We shouldn't have put you on the spot in front of all the leadership.
請坐  柯蒂斯
Have a seat, Curtis.
我們知道你必須堅守立場
We know that you have an obligation to take a firm stance,
但承諾福利改革是你競選的核心
but entitlement reform is something you ran on,
現在唾手可得了
and now it's within your grasp.
說說你的顧慮吧
So tell us your fears.
顧慮就是共和黨又會贏一把
That the Democrats get another win.
我們在中期選舉中失利
We suffer in the midterms,
下一屆國會就會廢除協議
and the next Congress dismantles the agreement.
你覺得我們在玩花招
You think we're being disingenuous.
我的選民不信任政府
My constituents don't trust the administration.
我不能讓他們覺得我們受到了矇騙
I can't have them thinking the wool's been pulled over our eyes.
如我所料  赫克特
As I suspected. Hector?
弗蘭克和我建議
Frank and I propose this:
我們加入一項簡單多數條款
We include a super majority point of order
十年內不再就這個問題進行新的立法討論
against revisiting the issue for 10 years.
白紙黑字寫下來
You have it in black and white.
達成一項長期的嚴肅承諾  不會被撤銷
A serious, long-term commitment with no opportunity to dismantle.
這是加在其他要求之上
And that's on top of everything else we asked for.
退伍軍人事務管理局和聯邦救災署的經費維持不變
VA services and FEMA stay at current levels.
其他機構的經費削減為你提議的80%到100%
Everything else at 80 to 100 percent of the cuts you propose.
你贏了  柯蒂斯
You get your win, Curtis.
我們只想避免災難
We just avoid disaster.
也許國家應該見識一下災難
Maybe the country needs to see what disaster looks like.
茶黨的影響力很大  而你又為他們宣傳
The Tea Party has a strong voice, and you're its bullhorn.
讓你的人民看到  這份影響力能決定法律
Show your people that voice can translate into law
而不僅僅是激昂的口號
and not just add to the noise.
15年內不得重談  10年不夠
15 years before revisitation. Not 10.
可以
Okay.
如果我們通過法案後  眾議院沒有通過
And if the House fails to pass the bill after we do,
你得公開譴責你們黨派造了這種僵局
you go on record blaming your own party for the gridlock.
我們這就算達成協議了
I believe we have a deal.
你在聽什麼
What are you listening to?
抱歉  我關...
I'm sorry. I'll turn...
別  很好聽  我能聽嗎
No, it's nice. Can I listen?
我的耳朵很乾淨  我保證
My ears are clean. I promise.
謝謝
Thanks.
-真美  -是啊
- It's beautiful. - Yeah.
好哀傷
It's so sad.
能讓我放鬆
It helps me relax.
今天很辛苦嗎
Long day?
我在客服中心上班
I work at a call center.
一小時打電話給200個陌生人  是挺辛苦
So, yeah. 200 strangers an hour.
我就不打擾你了
I'll leave you alone.
你大概也不想再和陌生人聊天了
You probably don't want to talk to another one.
沒關係  你不掛我電話就行
It -- it's all right. As long as you don't hang up on me.
你會和他們聊天嗎  那些陌生人
Do you ever just talk to them? The strangers?
我們不允許
We're not allowed to.
換了我  肯定想問問他們是什麼樣
All I would want to do is ask them about who they are.
你呢  你做什麼工作
What about you? What do you do?
我...在書店和託兒所上班
I, um, I work at the bookstore and the daycare center.
冬離友誼會  通往平靜之路
別人第一次給我宣傳冊時
I had that same look on my face
我也是這個表情
the first time somebody handed me one of those.
我只是...不信教
Yeah, I'm -- I'm just -- I'm not religious.
留著吧  看不看都無所謂
Just keep it. Check it out, or don't.
我們那兒有非常棒的音樂
We've got really good music there.
謝謝你
I'm -- thank you.
眾議院向參議院提交了一份法案
The House sent a bill to the Senate.
和弗蘭克期待的反饋完全不同
What Frank wants to send back bears zero resemblance.
因為那是兩黨聯合的  不像我們的這份
Because it's bipartisan. Unlike ours.
聽著像弗蘭克的話
That sounds like something Frank would say.
我不是弗蘭克
I'm not Frank.
他是你辦公室的常客
He has a desk in your office.
如果法案在參議院通過
If this bill passes in the Senate --
不可能
It won't.
我們得有所準備  鮑勃
We should be prepared, Bob.
那我就拭目以待了
Well, I'm prepared to wait and see.
下午愉快  女士們
Have a good afternoon, ladies.
女士們
"Ladies"?
他受到了威脅
He's threatened.
蠢豬一個
He's a pig.
給他點時間
Give him time.
以前他身邊有兩個中年白人男子
He used to have two white middle-aged guys at his side.
現在他只能依靠一個黑人和一個小他20歲的女人
Now he's got a black guy and a woman 20 years his junior.
可這女人會開槍
Who knows how to shoot a rifle.
我們得繼續勸他
We just need to keep at him.
什麼事
Yes?
凱特琳娜·羅德里格斯在四號線
Catalina Rodriguez is on line four.
你先下去
Give me a moment.
凱特琳娜
Catalina.
泰德告訴我是你幹的
Ted told me it was you.
你在聽嗎
You there?
是的  我在聽
Yes, I'm here.
媒體對我們窮追不捨
The press won't leave us alone.
他們連續幾周跑過來
For weeks they're showing up,
想拍到我和艾米莉的照片
trying to get pictures of me and Emily.
不是我洩的密
It wasn't me.
只有你知情
You're the only one who knew.
我不知道事情怎麼會洩露
I do-- I don't know how the story got out.
泰德何必對我撒謊呢
Why would Ted lie abut that?
我不知道  也許他感到羞愧
I don't know. Maybe -- maybe he's ashamed.
那我該怎麼辦  他們什麼時候才會放過我們
So what do I do? When will they leave us alone?
我也不知道  凱特琳娜
I -- I don't know, Catalina.
我受不了這樣的生活
I can't live like this.
我很抱歉  我不知該說什麼
I'm s-- I'm sorry. I don't know what to say.
艾米莉還好嗎
How -- how is Emily doing?
凱特琳娜
Catalina?
他自信滿滿
He's very confident.
沒錯  但他有那個本事嗎
Yeah, but does he have what it takes?
等他拿出媒體方案就知道了
We'll see when I get his media plan.
他個性如何
What about his personality?
迷人  直接  思維縝密
Charming. Direct. Very thorough.
他找到了86年我們第一次一起接受採訪的錄影
He found our first interview together, in '86.
我很想重溫一下  他有副本嗎
I would love to see that. Does he have a copy?
我想沒有  電視臺只允許他在臺裡看
I don't think so. The TV station made him watch it there.
我們該錄下來給總統和第一夫人看的
We should screen that for the president and the first lady.
讓他們學學怎麼接受採訪
Show 'em how it's done.
克里斯蒂娜
Christina...
她怎麼了
What about her?
你有沒有注意到她和總統有什麼不正常
Have you noticed anything strange between her and the president?
什麼意思
How do you mean?
昨天我在走道裡碰見他們
I passed them in the hall yesterday.
他們看上去  我說不好  很親密
And they seem -- I don't know -- very intimate.
預備會議上他們是挺熱絡的
They did seem cozy at the prep session.
你覺得...
Do you think...?
不  不一定
No. Not necessarily.
不過這想法挺有意思
An interesting thought, though.
抱歉打擾  先生
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
我們在吃午飯
We're having lunch.
共和黨人變卦了
The Republicans are backing out.
門多薩的幕僚長給我提了醒
Mendoza's chief of staff just gave me the heads-up.
馬上幫我接門多薩
Get Mendoza on the phone.
是柯蒂斯·哈斯  他臨陣退縮了
It's Curtis Haas. He got cold feet.
籠子  差不多像那樣  不過
Cages. It's really kinda like but,
但大家會看  挺逗的
you know, people look at 'em. It's kind of fun.
我收到你郵件了
I got your email.
你現在有空嗎
Now good for you?
當然  我過會兒打給你
Yeah, sure. Can I call you right back?
你究竟想問什麼
What exactly did you need to know?
我們在做網路戰的後續報道
We're doing some follow-up pieces on the cyber warfare thing.
我就想問問內行人知不知道
I just wanted to get a layman's understanding
中國人會如何越過防火牆
of how the Chinese might get through a firewall.
挺複雜的  不過我可以演示下基本原理
It's a bit complicated, but I could show you the basics.
那足夠了
That's all I need.
輸入響應碼
我們使用的是標準多層體繫結構
We use a standard N-tier architecture.
就像多層麵包做成的大三明治
Think of it like a big sandwich with layers of bread.
每層之間夾著生菜  番茄  烤牛肉之類的
Between each is the lettuce, the tomato, the roast beef, whatever.
我現在輸入的是組織程式碼
What I'm pulling up here is the org code,
隔離了資料庫
which, uh, separates the database --
該死  我忘了馬上要和銷售部門開會
Shit. I forgot there's a meeting with sales in a couple minutes.
你想晚點繼續嗎
You want to do this later?
不用  我現在跑過去
No. I'll just run over
跟他們說我要晚幾分鐘到  馬上回來
and let them know I'll be a few minutes late. Be right back.
好  我就在這兒
Cool. I'll be here.
我拿到手機了
很好  發送請求密碼
好的
Okay.
快點快點
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
來了
There.
快回覆啊
Come on.
我進去了  幹得好
晚上9點  西北區  哥倫比亞街  6697號見
好
Okay.
切記
刪除簡訊
好嘞
Go.
出什麼事了
Something wrong?
我找不著手機了  真奇怪
Can't find my phone. It -- it's weird.
剛剛還在的
I had it just a minute ago.
找到了  不好意思
Here it is. Sorry about that.
沒事
No problem.
那個多層體繫結構
So the, uh, N-tier architecture.
我剛說的那個高科技三明治
The high-tech sandwich I was talking about.
我以為門多薩願意合作
I thought Mendoza was willing to work with us.
他是願意  問題在柯蒂斯·哈斯
He is. The problem is Curtis Haas.
你跟他談過了嗎
And have you spoken with him?
他辦公室不回我們電話
His office isn't returning our calls.
門多薩也是
Neither is Mendoza's --
我不該讓步的
I should've stuck to my guns.
明天下午才開始投票
The vote isn't until tomorrow afternoon.
我一早就會聯繫門多薩
I'll reach out to Mendoza first thing in the --
這可是國情諮文  弗蘭克
This is the State of the Union, Frank.
我不能陷入尷尬境地
I won't be left in limbo.
如果我們得重寫演講
If we need to start rewriting that speech now,
我一分鐘也不想耽誤
I don't want to waste a minute.
我能扭轉局面  先生
I can turn this around, sir.
雷蒙德告訴我這是你的點子
You know, Raymond told me this was your idea.
做出妥協
To pursue this compromise.
只是提出建議
I suggested it as an option.
他說是你逼他蹚這渾水的
He said you bullied him into it,
他認為這是個錯誤的決定
that he thought it was a -- a mistake.
如果他這麼反對  他就應該勸阻你
If he felt so strongly, he should have advised you otherwise.
雷蒙德不是政客
Raymond is not a politician.
他依賴於我們的政治意見
He relies on our political expertise
正如我們依靠他的商業頭腦
as much as we rely on his business acumen.
或許我們應該到真出現問題再相互指責
Maybe we shouldn't point fingers until there's a problem.
你管這不叫問題
Oh, you wouldn't call this a problem.
在成為問題之前解決掉就不是問題
Not if it's solved before it becomes one.
我要的是個能管理好國會的副總統
You see, I wanted a Vice President who can manage Congress.
而不是個不自量力的人
Not one who bites off more than he can chew.
那就相信你做出了正確的決定  先生
Then have faith you made the right choice, sir.
我的信念正在迅速地消失殆盡了
Whatever faith I have is quickly evaporating.
別給政府丟臉  弗蘭克
Don't humiliate the administration, Frank.
你也是其中一員了
You're part of it now.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我們談完了
We're done.
謝謝  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
幫我接內線
Give me the private line, please.
塔斯克擋我道  古德溫對我窮追不捨
Tusk is blocking my way. Goodwin at my heels.
現在一步也不能錯
There can be no false steps now.
越往上爬  爾虞我詐越多
The higher up the mountain, the more treacherous the path.
盧卡斯·古德溫去找她了
Lucas Goodwin went up to visit her.
他們可能也會來找你
They may be looking for you.
沒人找過我  應該沒人知道我在這兒
Nobody's contacted me. I don't think anyone knows I'm here.
那我們要確保你不會被人發現
Then we need to make sure it stays that way.
避免不必要的交談
Don't speak to anyone you don't have to.
不要去不必要的地方
Don't go anywhere you don't need to be.
告訴我你聽到我說的了
Tell me you heard what I said.
聽到了  我知道了
I heard you. I get it.
我沒事
I'm fine.
-敷點冰  -我說了我沒事
- Put some ice on it. - I said it's okay.
這是什麼
What is this?
你現在還翻我的垃圾嗎
What, are you going through my garbage now?
在公交上別人給我的
Someone gave it to me on the bus.
有人聯繫你  就來告訴我
You let me know if anyone contacts you.
抱歉我來晚了
Sorry I'm late.
沒事
No worries.
現在你要紋多少
How much more you want to do right now?
填滿這一塊嗎
Fill in this area?
嗯  然後下面再多加一個罌粟
Yeah. And, uh, one more poppy down here.
一次做這麼多啊
That's a lot for one sitting.
我知道
I know.
好吧
Okay.
弗蘭西斯
Francis?
這就走嗎
You're heading in?
門多薩起的早
Mendoza's an early riser.
你會解決好的
You'll figure this out.
我得證明副總統不吃素的
I need to prove what the Vice President is capable of.
別向他們證明  向我證明
Don't prove it to them. Prove it to me.
柯蒂斯抓著我的要害  弗蘭克
Curtis has me by the tea bags, Frank.
沒他我的黨派就要亂套
I don't have a working majority without him.
可他不是多數黨領袖
He wasn't elected leader.
是沒錯  但我也得選邊站
True. But I have to pick my battles.
你要是在預算問題上無法控制他
If you can't control him on budgetary issues --
不光是他  還有聽命於他的15個參議員
It's not just him. It's the 15 senators he has under his thumb.
沒他們支援我就不能連任
I won't be the leader next year if they turn on me.
他想我們求他  把他找來
So he wants to be courted. Sit him down --
我試過和他談了  但他不肯讓步
I already tried talking to him. He wouldn't budge.
那我們一起去跟他談
Then we'll both talk to him.
他已經表明立場了
He's made his position clear.
我們都在這張桌子旁握手了
We all shook hands at this table.
我最多只能保證限制替代修正案
The most I can do is put the substitute amendment
表決前的辯論
on the floor with limited debate.
你們那邊公開怎麼說隨你們便
Now, your people can say whatever they want for the record.
但我們會投票否決修正案
But we're gonna vote the amendment down.
我對象徵性姿態不敢興趣
I am not interested in symbolic gestures.
我只能做到這樣
That's all I can offer.
你的勇氣哪去了
Where's your courage?
我權力有限  弗蘭克
My power has limits, Frank.
再有五個共和黨人  你那票就定勝負了
Five Republicans makes you the deciding vote.
現在很難說
Now, it's highly doubtful
我們能不能讓他們違反黨派意志投票
we can get them to vote against their own party.
但他們可以棄權
But they might abstain.
那需要10人棄權
You'd need 10.
福利問題是共和黨人的長期追求
Entitlement is the Republicans' white whale.
我至少能說通兩個人
I can get at least two of 'em to flip.
那就只需要六票棄權
And you'd only need six abstaining.
艾瑞克森已經在打電話了
Erikson's already making calls.
唐納
Donner?
還有普拉斯科
And Pulaski.
給我一份名單  我找幾個人一起上陣
All right. Get me a call list so I can tag-team with him.
在這兒
Got it right here.
我們得使狠招
We have to get medieval.
要說議會程式
When it comes to parliamentary procedure,
沒有哪條規定我不知道  先生
there's not a rule I don't know, sir.
給我找到能鑽空子的
Find me the ones we can bend.
馬克  你是個明白人
Mark, you're a sensible man.
是  我知道  我懂
Yes, I -- I know -- I understand.
如果  跟你說
What if -- tell you what.
如果你選區內的兩家退伍軍人醫院  對  兩家
What if both VA hospitals in your district -- yes, both of them.
別掛  誰
Hold on. Who?
莫里亞蒂
Moriarty.
我答應給他的牲牛研究中心撥款
I promised him an amendment for his bovine research center.
這就有六票了
That makes six.
馬克  如果我能給兩家醫院提供資金
Mark, if I can get you funding for both,
你願跟我們合作嗎
are you with us?
非常好
Excellent.
你這幾天來白宮
You come by the White House
跟我共進午餐吧
and have lunch with me sometime soon.
再見  數目夠了
Bye-bye. We have the numbers.
你打斷點名之後
Once you break the quorum call
會有些麻煩
it's gonna be a little tricky.
我們路上說
Tell me on the way.
先生  先生
Sir. Sir.
-我們票數可能不佔多數  -什麼
- We might not have a majority. - What?
民主黨在挖牆腳
The Dems are poaching people.
唐納  普拉斯基  可能還有別人
Donner, Pulaski. Maybe more.
投票通過修正案嗎
Voting for the amendment?
部分支援  其餘棄權  我還在查是誰
Some. Others abstaining. I'm still trying to figure out who.
我們得推遲  弄清到底是怎麼回事
We need to delay and figure out what the fuck's going on.
點名  離休會還有49小時
Quorum call. There's 49 hours until the recess.
一小時叫一個人來
We call a name an hour.
艾文戴爾先生
Mr. Avendale?
到
Here.
抱歉  你坐了我的位置
Excuse me. I do believe you're sitting in my chair.
德魯裡先生  現在進行到哪裡了
Mr. Drewry, what is the order of business.
我們正在點名  先生
We are in a quorum call, sir.
那你怎麼不點名呢
Then why aren't you calling the roll?
在點名  先生  不著急
We are, sir. In a deliberate manner.
速度快點吧
Let's speed it up.
布朗先生
Mr. Brown?
到
Here.
動作再快點
More expeditious than that.
-博爾先生  -到
- Mr. Burr? - Here.
-坎特維爾女士  -到
- Ms. Cantwell? - Here.
西里尼先生
Mr. Cerini?
到
Check.
康維爾
Cornwall?
到
Here.
科森先生
Mr. Colson?
道斯特女士
Ms. Douster
到
Here.
法定人數夠了  我們票數不夠
They have a quorum. We don't have the numbers.
出去  讓我們的人都出去
Out. Let's get all our people out.
-達默爾先生  達令先生  -到
- Mr. Demerell. Mr. Darling. - Here.
-達斯瓦尼先生  -到
- Mr. Daswani. - Here.
-唐納先生  -再快點
- Mr. Donner. - Faster.
道本先生  德懷爾先生
Mr. Dobben, Mr. Dwyer.
-埃倫伯格  安格  艾瑞克森  -到
- Erinburgh, Engel, Erikson. - Here.
菲爾德  法瑞森  詹特里
Feld, Ferrison, Gentry.
哈斯先生
Mr. Haas.
-懷特豪斯先生  -到
- Mr. Whitehouse. - Here.
維克先生  懷登先生
Mr. Wicker. Mr. Wyden.
副總統先生  沒有達到法定人數
Mr. President, a quorum is not present.
主席允許少數黨領袖  艾瑞克森先生發言
The chair recognizes the minority leader, Mr. Erikson.
主席先生
Mr. President,
我提議命令警衛官
I move to direct the sergeant at arms
強制缺席參議員到場
to compel the attendance of absent Senators;
對於無故缺席的所有參議員
that warrants for the arrests of all senators not sick nor excused
請會議主席簽發逮捕令予以逮捕
be issued under the signature of the presiding officer.
對動議進行表決  同意者說"贊成"
The question is on the motion. All those in favor say "Aye"
贊成
Aye.
反對者說"反對"
All those opposed, "Nay."
反對
Nay.
同意者佔多數  動議通過
The ayes have it, and the motion is agreed to.
我命令警衛官
The sergeant of arms is hereby instructed
強制缺席參議員到場
to compel the attendance of absent senators.
回國會的感覺真好
It feels good to be back in Congress.
現在民主黨人已經授予國會警察
The Democrats have now empowered the Capitol Police
在必要時逮捕缺席參議員的權利
to arrest absent members if necessary.
共和黨參議員柯蒂斯·哈斯
According to Republican Senator Curtis Haas,
福利改革修正案的堅決反對者之一
one of the staunchest opponents of the entitlement amendment,
這樣說道  副總統正在
the vice president is, quote,
"用暴政取代民主
"Replacing democracy with tyranny.
他已經將參議院變成了國會裡的極權國家"
He's transformed the Senate into a police state within the Capitol."
但是
But --
現在想躲避媒體更難了
It'll be even harder to stay out of the news now.
那為什麼還要一起接受採訪
Then why the joint interview?
我又看了一遍南卡羅來納的採訪
I watched the South Carolina one again.
說服他們給了我一份拷貝
Convinced them to make me a copy.
非常有感染力  給你
It's powerful. Here you go.
我猜你可能想留一份
I thought you might want it.
採訪中有一個瞬間  你用手幫他捋頭髮
There's a moment where you ran your fingers through his hair.
非常親密  非常有人情味
It's intimate and human.
單是那一個瞬間就足以讓我為你丈夫投票
That moment alone would've made me want to vote for your husband.
像這樣的小事  能給你幾個月的清淨
Something like that will buy you months of flying beneath the radar.
你想讓誰來進行採訪
And who do you have in mind to conduct the interview?
這代表我被錄用了嗎
Does this mean I have the job?
這代表你還沒出局
It means you still haven't been ruled out.
我就當是有進步了
Well, I'll consider that progress.
這裡是民主黨議員的衣帽間  赫克特
This is the Democratic cloak room, Hector.
你們的在另一邊
Yours is on the other side.
你的招數不會成功的
What you're doing won't work.
有可能會  所以你大老遠的跑過來了
It might. Which is why you made the long walk over here.
冰水
Ice water?
我的人正坐著各種交通工具趕過來
I have my people in planes, trains, and automobiles.
我只需要六票達到法定人數
All I need is six to make my quorum.
想想我有26票能幹什麼
Think what I can do with 26 votes.
現在我都有45票了
And I've got 45.
你的人再怎麼趕也沒這麼快吧
You won't be able to get your planes and trains back here fast enough.
我願賭一把
I'll roll those dice.
會議警衛官的工作做得非常好
The sergeant at arms is very good at his job.
這樣正可以讓柯蒂斯明白  究竟誰是老大
And this is a perfect way to show Curtis who's in charge.
我這是在幫你  赫克特
I'm doing you a favor, Hector.
告訴我你想要什麼
Tell me what you want.
我一直想要的東西  我們達成的協議
What I've always wanted. The package we shook hands on.
然後我就把參議院還給你
Then I'll give you your Senate back.
他們不能自願回來嗎
They can't come back voluntarily.
選六個演技最好的出來
Pick your six best actors.
我們不能妥協  赫克特
We can't give in, Hector.
如果你按黨派路線走  我們就不會落到這個境地
We wouldn't be in this situation had you towed the party line.
門多薩先生到場
Mr. Mendoza is present.
表示抗議
Under protest.
康維爾女士到場
Ms. Cornwall is present.
表示抗議
Under protest.
厄爾曼先生到場  沃爾什先生到場
Mr. Ullman is present. Mr. Walsh is present.
道斯特女士到場
Ms. Douster is present.
哈斯先生到場
And Mr. Haas is present.
主席先生  法定人數已經夠了
Mr. President, a quorum is now present.
你通過修正案吧  我會阻撓主法案的通過
You can pass the amendment. I'll just filibuster the main bill.
不  你不會的
No, you won't.
看我會不會
Watch me.
儘管我特別想看你憋兩天尿的樣子
As much as I'd like to see you hold your piss for two days,
但我們已經和赫克特達成協議了
we struck a deal with Hector.
替代修正案通過
The passage of the substitute amendment
主法案就也通過
constitutes passage of the main bill.
這我並不知情
I wasn't informed of that.
要多留意小字附條款  柯蒂斯
Pay attention to the fine print, Curtis.
這比協議本身重要的多
It's far more important than the selling price.
我們開始吧
Let's go.
現在立刻點名投票
I want an immediate call of the roll.
一秒鐘時間都不要浪費
Don't let half a second pass.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
法定人數已經夠了
A quorum is present.
關於採納HR 934號法案的
The question is on the adoption of the substitute
替代修正案
amendment to HR 934.
贊成或是反對
The yeas and nays have been ordered,
書記官將開始點名投票
and the clerk will call the roll.
艾伯納先生
Mr. Abner?
贊成
Aye.
艾文戴爾先生
Mr. Avendale?
贊成
Aye.
布朗先生
Mr. Brown?
我想為HR 934號法案提出一項修正案
I'd like to propose an amendment to HR 934
哈斯先生  請不要破壞秩序  點名投票已經開始
Mr. Haas, you are out of order. The roll call has begun.
書記官將會繼續進行點名投票
The clerk will continue to call the roll.
布朗先生  博爾先生
Mr. Brown? Mr. Burr?
贊成
Aye.
坎特維爾女士
Ms. Cantwell?
贊成
Aye.
西里尼先生
Mr. Cerini?
贊成
Aye.
蔡斯先生
Mr. Chess?
贊成
Aye.
康維爾女士
Ms. Cornwall?
反對
Nay.
科森先生
Mr. Colson?
我很高興你能來
I'm glad you came.
是啊  我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
你覺得怎麼樣
What'd you think?
音樂非常美妙
The music was really beautiful.
跟你想的不一樣嗎
Not what you expected?
我也不知道會是什麼樣
I wasn't sure what to expect.
我叫麗薩
I'm Lisa.
瑞秋  抱歉
Rachel. Sorry.
沒事  我們裡面有餅乾和蛋糕  如果你
No. We've got cookies and cake inside, if you...
我覺得我還是...
I think I'm gonna...
如果你想見見我的一些朋友
If you want to meet some of my friends.
-行啊  好  -行嗎
- Yeah. Okay. - Yeah?
-行  -走吧
- Yeah. Yeah. - Okay.
該把"奇蹟創造者"寫進你的簡歷  弗蘭克
We should add "Miracle worker" to your resume, Frank.
拉撒路的魔術倒是精彩
Lazarus makes for a good magic act,
聖經故事:馬大和馬利亞的兄弟  死後4天耶穌使他復活
但如果那混蛋當初沒死
but life would have been a lot easier
日子會輕鬆得多
if the bastard hadn't died in the first place.
總統本來要發脾氣  但我安撫住他了
The president wanted to go ballistic, but I calmed him down.
我說  別擔心  弗蘭克會解決問題的
I said, "Don't worry. Frank'll pull this out.
是嗎  我不會責怪你兩面派  雷蒙德
Did you? I don't blame you for being two-faced, Raymond.
這是厲害的政治手腕  但不能被人發現
It's good politics, as long as you don't get caught at it.
弗蘭克  如果你認為我
Now, Frank, if you think that I --
沒關係  雷蒙德  主會原諒你  晚安
It's okay, Raymond. Jesus forgives you. Goodnight.
有人嗎
Hello?
想來點酒嗎
Care for some wine?
不用了
No.
進來點
Step in the room.
近一點  再近一點
Closer. Closer.
說一下你的名字和日期
State your name and the date.
等等  為什麼  我
Wait, why? I --
請說一下你的名字和日期
State your name and the date, please.
盧卡斯·古德溫  2月13日
Lucas Goodwin. February 13th.
年份
Year.
2014年
2014.
你現在或曾經在
Are you currently or have you ever been a member of the --
這是幹什麼
What -- what -- what is this?
你現在或曾經在
Are you currently or have you ever been a member
執法機構工作過嗎
of any law enforcement agency?
我已經告訴過你我沒有了
I already told you I wasn't.
兩步驗證
Two-step verification.
不  我沒有  以前也沒有
No, I'm not. And I haven't.
那你現在或曾經向執法機構
Are you currently or have you ever been
提供過情報嗎
an informant for law enforcement?
沒有
No.
你覺得自己被跟蹤了嗎
You think you might have been followed?
過去幾周發生過什麼奇怪的事嗎
Anything strange the past few weeks?
這個...你知道嗎
Th-- this is -- you know what?
這讓我很不舒服
This is making me feel uncomfortable --
我們不是鬧著玩的
We're not fucking around here.
如果你認為聯調局沒查過你的郵件
If you think the FBI hasn't been tracking your posts,
那你就太天真了
then you're naive.
你覺得他們知道我的身份嗎
You think they know who I am?
不知道  你隱藏得很好
No. You hid yourself well.
你要對《先驅報》做什麼
What are you going to do with the Herald.
不做什麼
Nothing.
那你為什麼想要訪問許可權
Then why did you want access?
我已經有訪問許可權了
I already had access.
我就是這樣聯繫你的
It's how I contacted you in the first place.
只是想知道你是不是來真的
Just needed to know if you were serious.
那是腰果
That's Cashew.
你為什麼要聯繫我
Why did you contact me?
因為你走投無路了
Because you're desperate.
我不喜歡當局
And I'm not fond of authority.
今天  在安德伍德副總統的主持下
Just today, under the leadership of Vice President Underwood,
參議院通過了HR 934號法案
the Senate passed HR 934,
同時通過了一個歷史性的福利改革修正案
along with an historic entitlement reform amendment.
通過將正常退休和提早退休的年齡
By raising the retirement age to 68 and 65
分別提高到68和65歲
for normal and early retirement, respectively,
我們將確保未來幾代人的福利得到保障
we will ensure entitlements for generations to come.
幾周後  等眾議院通過這項法案
And when the House passes that bill in a few weeks,
對此我完全有信心
as I fully expect it to do,
我們就能結束政府的開銷凍結
we will put the government freeze to rest.
我們將繼續為我們的國家服務
We will continue the business of serving our country,
而不是讓國家癱瘓
rather than paralyzing it.
這是美國人民應得的
The American people deserve no less.
我們站在民主的聖壇上
We stand at the altar of democracy.
讓我們站在一起
Let us stand together.
我跟傑姬談過  我會在眾議院支援你
I spoke to Jackie. You have my support in the House.
但現在眾議院還沒通過呢
But it hasn't passed the House yet.
在交給總統前  還長路漫漫
There's a long march before it arrives on the president's desk.
至於我  我以前總在鏡頭邊緣
As for me, I used to be on the edge of the frame.
現在只有三英尺遠了
Now I'm only three feet away.
■
一個議案先在參議院表決  然後在眾議院表決
眾議院表決時  可以自己起草一個版本
也可以直接拿參議院的版本進行投票
本集中弗蘭克想讓眾議院直接拿參議院通過的版本進行表決
這樣更高效  如果有兩個版本
雙方還得把兩個版本綜合在一起
各自再投票一次  然後才能給總統簽字  生效成為法律
■
美國憲法規定副總統是參議院的主席
但是平時副總統不干預參議員事務
只有在投票出現平局或大的會議時才出席
而本集中弗蘭克打破了常規  利用規則主持參議院投票
所以才會對多數黨領袖說"就把參議院還給你"
■
2013年9月  德克薩斯州茶黨參議院泰德·科魯茲
鼓動同僚反對歐巴馬醫保法案
要求國會預演算法案同醫保法案落實掛鉤
9月24日至25日  泰德·科魯茲連續在參議院發言21小時19分鐘
為茶黨造出極大聲勢
由於科魯茲等國會兩院中的茶黨成員在預算問題上堅持強硬立場
而總統歐巴馬為了搞臭共和黨的名聲也拒絕談判
美國聯邦政府於10月1日被迫"停擺"  關張大吉
停擺持續了16天  兩黨在聲望均遭到極大打擊的情況下
不得不坐在一起  達成預算協議